winspark.com 2019-06-06

# WinsPark - Privacy and Security Policy

As an operator based in the EU, Hermione is GDPR compliant and entirely committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.  

This Privacy Policy outlines our practices with respect to collecting, using and disclosing the Private Information we gather through your use of our services and website, and relays the rights of individuals in relation to the personal data we hold.

The Privacy Policy is a part of our Terms of Service and is incorporated therein by reference. It is likewise an integral part of Winspark User Agreement. Accordingly, when you access or use the Winspark website, you automatically agree to our collection, use, and disclosure of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**We collect your information in order to:**

  * Comply with our regulatory duties, obligations and responsibilities. 
  * Conform to legal requirements or comply with legal processes under any valid and applicable legislation and/or competent authority (meaning any authority having any governmental, juridical or regulatory jurisdiction over us).
  * For the purpose of reporting  potential or suspected crime, including money laundering or  fraud. 

If you do not agree, or are not comfortable with any part of this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Winspark website and services.

According to the new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), Winspark commits to taking the following customer’s rights into consideration:

**Breach Notification**

Where a data breach is likely to result in a risk to the rights and freedoms of individuals, the Company is obliged to inform all customers within 72 hours of first having become aware of such a breach.

**Right to Access**

Winspark’s clients have the right to know whether or not personal data is being processed, where, and for what purpose. For more detailed information, customers can check the following sections of the privacy Policy (below): 

**  \- The type of information we collect **  
 **  \- How we collect information?**  
 **  \- How we use the information we collect **  
 **  \- With whom we share the information**  
 **  \- Retention of Personal Information**

Upon request, we will provide our customers with a copy of the collected personal data in an electronic format. 

**Right to be Forgotten  **

Winspark’s clients have the right to request their personal data to be erased and cease the further dissemination of their data by the Company or any third parties. It should also be taken into consideration that this right requires the Company to compare the individual’s rights to the “public interest in the availability of the data” when regarding such requests. 

**Data Portability  **

Winspark’s customers have the right to request their previously provided personal data. Data portability allows customers to use this data with other operators as well.

**The type of information we collect  **

**We collect two types of information from our users:  **

**1\. Non-personal Information**  \- the first type of information is unidentified and non-identifiable information pertaining to a user, which may be made available or gathered via your use of our services . User’s Non-Personal information includes, Inter alia, IP address, ISP and operating system types, internet browsers and dates, as well as times our service is accessed.   
 **2\. Personal Information**  \- the second type of information is individually identifiable information, namely information that identifies an individual or may with reasonable effort identify an individual. When you use our Services, you will be asked to provide Personal Information. User’s personal information includes, Inter alia, User’s name, address, phone number, e-mail address, credit card number and financial information. 

If we combine Personal Information with Non-Personal Information, the combined information will be treated as Personal Information for as long as it remains combined.  

**How we collect information  **

We collect all the Account Information that you provide us with during the Account creation process and your personal information when you register to become a member of our site or voluntarily provide when you use the site / communicate with us. In order to offer the best possible service and to minimise any risk of unfairness, we keep records of your gaming history and financial transactions history. We also collect information when certain changes in a customer’s account are applied upon a customer’s wish, such as changes in email address, registration of a new payment method, etc.  

**Cookies  **

We use cookies (a piece of data sent from a website and stored in a user's web browser while the user is browsing that website) to track your use in Winspark, provide you with a more personalized user experience, and allow you to sign in and begin playing instantly when visiting the website.

You may remove the cookies by following the instructions of your device preferences. You may also find more information about cookies here. Note, however, that if you choose to disable cookies, some features of our service may not operate properly and your online experience may be compromised as a result.

For more information please review our Cookies Policy below.

**How we use the information we collect    **

We use and share Personal Information in the manners described in this Privacy Policy. The Personal Information will be disclosed to a third-party only to the extent required for the specific purpose, as stipulated in this Privacy Policy, and in such a case, we require the relevant third-party to agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy. 

We use the collected personal details and information only for its intended purpose, such as; allowing us to communicate and send you your Withdrawals. We may also contact you via email to provide you with information regarding new software updates, terms & conditions updates, policies, and promotional material.

We may use the personal information that you provided to set up your account and provide you with the services (including billing), and to administer and manage your account and provide you with promotional updates regarding such products or services.   

We will not send you unsolicited information regarding any third-party commercial offers or advertisements.

**With whom we share the information?**

We do not rent, sell, or share your Personal Information with third parties  except as described in this Privacy Policy. The Personal Information will be disclosed to Recipients only to the extent required for the specific purpose, as stipulated in this Privacy Policy.

We may occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including, without limitation, identity verification and authentication; payment processing; communication of promotional material; information relating to our and our partners’ products and services, and the provision of software. We will only provide these companies with information that is reasonably required to perform the service, and they will be prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. When any of our third-party contractors or partners collect and/or have access to your personal information, we require that they adhere to our stated Privacy policies and protect the confidentiality of your personal information. 

We may also disclose Personal Information, or any information you submitted if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is helpful or reasonably necessary to: (i) enforce our policies (including our Agreement), including investigations of potential violations thereof; (ii) investigate, detect, prevent, or take action on illegal activities or other wrongdoing, suspected fraud or security issues; (iii) to establish or exercise our rights to defend ourselves against legal claims; (iv) prevent harm to the rights, property, or safety of ourselves, our users, yourself or any third-party. 

**Transfer of information  **

Winspark is SSL-Secured. When your (Personal and Non-Personal) Information passes from your computer to our server, we ensure that your personal information and all other sensitive data is transferred securely over the internet and kept strictly confidential, augmented by the most recently updated firewall technologies. 

Since we operate globally, it may be necessary to transfer your Personal Information to countries outside the European Union. The data protection and other laws of these countries may not be as comprehensive as those in the European Union. In such instances, we will take steps to ensure that a similar level of protection is given to your Personal Information. Note that by using our site and our services, you consent to the transfer of your Personal Information to countries outside the European Union.   

**Retention of personal information  **

Please note that unless you instruct us otherwise, we retain the information we collect for as long as needed to provide our services.   
You can review and modify your information at any time by contacting Customer Support. For your own protection, you will be required to provide proof of your identity, including a valid identification card, credit card under your name, address, contact email and a valid phone number. 

Note, however, we may be required to continue to retain records containing your information for legitimate business, regulatory, compliance and/or legal purposes. We may also rectify, replenish, or remove incomplete or inaccurate information at any time and at our own discretion.  

**Winnings**

We believe that your good fortune is ultimately your own business. We therefore keep all our members' winnings and withdrawals strictly confidential and private. That notwithstanding, we may publicise certain details regarding winnings for promotional purposes, including the prize (amount won), the game’s name, winner’s first name and first letter of his last name, his/her country and city. 

Note that Winspark users who win a prize may still be requested to provide their consent to be photographed, and in such an event, we may use and publicise their photograph for promotional purposes - but only if so permitted. 

Like all other information, our winnings information is stored in a secure operating environment. 

**Payment Processing  **

Our payment process is focused on user-friendliness and comfort of use, thus offering a variety of payment methods. Winspark offers a wide host of deposit options and fast cash-outs. All the options are user friendly and highly secure. Please check our Deposit  and Cash-out  policies for more information. 

All credit and debit card transactions are processed by Hermione Ltd. - a corporation incorporated under the laws of Cyprus. 

Should you have additional questions or concerns regarding the processing of payments, please do not hesitate to contact our Customer Support center at any time. We are always happy to assist. 

**Marketing  **

The Company may, from time to time, offer you special promotions. Note that promotions begin at 00:00 and end at 23:59 UTC on specified dates, unless stated otherwise in the promotions’ Terms & Conditions. The option to view the Terms & Conditions will be one click away in every promotion.

Winspark will use your Personal Information, such as your name, home address, email address, telephone number etc., for the purpose of providing you with promotional materials concerning our products and services including our website and applications which relate to Winspark’s business partners and affiliates that we believe may interest you.

You may be notified about the promotions by various means, including but not limited to (i) email (ii) phone (iii) SMS (iv) additional windows or pop-ups opening from within the game platform. 

We may also share and disclose Personal Information with our Marketing Affiliates for the purpose of providing you with different marketing offers, which we, or our Marketing Affiliates, believe are relevant to you. Our Marketing Affiliates may use this Personal Information for different marketing techniques, such as direct email, post, SMS and telephone marketing purposes.

Please note: we are, by law, obliged to have your consent to receiving such promotional or marketing materials before sending them. We thus provide you with the option to opt out at any time (below). 

**Opting out**

As part of the account registration process, we offer those registering with Winspark the option to opt out from receiving information regarding future events, offers and promotions. 

If you are interested in opting out, 'uncheck' the relevant box during the registration process, or contact us for assistance. 

 \- To unsubscribe from our marketing mailing list, please send our support team ([support@Winspark.com](mailto:Support@winspark.com)) a blank email with the text "remove" in the subject line OR click the ‘unsubscribe’ button in our marketing mailers.    
 \- To update your marketing preferences at any time, contact Customer Service.  
 \- To opt out of third-party analytics, email [support@Winspark.com](mailto:Support@winspark.com) and include your device identifier. Once processed, our third-party analytics provider will discontinue any analytics on that particular device. 

**Corporate Transaction  **

We may share Information - including Personal Information - in the event of a corporate transaction (e.g. sale of a substantial part of our business, merger, consolidation or sale of an asset or transfer in the operation thereof) of the Company. In the event of the above, the acquiring company or transferee will assume the rights and obligations as described in this Privacy Policy. 

**Minors  **

Our services are not designated for users under the age of 18. If you are under 18, you should neither download or use the services we offer nor provide any Personal Information to us. Since we reserve the right to access and verify all the Personal Information we collect, in the event that we become aware that you are under the age of 18, we will immediately discard such information.   
If you have any reason to believe that a minor has shared any information with us, we urge you to contact us at [support@Winspark.com](mailto:Support@winspark.com) as soon as possible.

Updates or amendments to the Privacy Policy 

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time, at our sole discretion, and the most current version will be posted on our website (as reflected in the "Last Revised" section). We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. In case of any material changes, we will notify you through our services or by email.

Such substantial changes will take effect seven (7) days after such notice was provided via any of the above mentioned methods. Otherwise, all other changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated “Last Revised” date, and your continued use of our services after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance of and agreement to be bound by those changes. 

Your continued use of the Services, following the notification of such amendments on our website, constitutes your acknowledgement of and consent to such amendments to the Privacy Policy and your agreement to be bound by the terms of such amendments.  

**User Choice and How to Contact Us  **

You may obtain a copy of your information held by us by contacting Customer services. Note, however, that (i) we require up to twenty eight (28) days’ notice to enable us to comply with such a request, and (ii) any such request is subject to a fee of $/€/£10 to meet our administrative costs

Should you experience any difficulties, we have implemented a professional customer support center ready to assist you 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. Please do not hesitate to contact our Support Centre. (Note that telephone calls to and from our Customer Service Department are recorded for training and security purposes.)

_This Privacy and Security Policy has been drafted in English. In the event of any discrepancy between the meanings of any translated versions of this Policy and the English language version, the meaning of the English language version shall prevail._

_This Privacy Policy was last revised on 2 September 2018._

**Cookies Policy**

Winspark uses cookies to deliver a better and more personalised service to users. This Cookies Policy explains what cookies are, how they are used on the Website and how to manage their use.

When you visit or access our website or applications operated by us, or when you interact or engage with our content (“Services”), we use (and authorize third parties to use) web beacons, cookies, pixel tags, scripts, tags, API and other "tracking technologies". These tracking technologies allow us to automatically collect information about you, your device and your online behaviour, in order to enhance your navigation on our site, improve our performance of services and customise your experience thereof. 

We also use this information to collect statistics about the usage of our services, perform analytics, deliver content which is tailored to your interests, and administer services to our users, advertisers, publishers, customers and partners.

**What is a Cookie?**

Cookies are small text files containing small amounts of information which are sent to and stored on your computer, smartphone or other device when you access a website. Each cookie is sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit or to another website that recognises that cookie. Cookies are ultimatley useful because they allow a website to recognise a user's device.

When active, a cookie can help make our services more user-friendly, for example by remembering your language preferences and settings. 

**Use of Cookies on the Website**

We use cookies on the website in a number of ways. This includes, but is not limited to, the following:  (a) to allow users to log on to their Winspark account; (b) to allow users to choose log-in preferences; (c) to monitor and collect information about transactions placed on the website; and (4) for fraud prevention purposes and generally to safeguard privacy.

Though cookies are generally used to improve and enhance user experience, some of the cookies we use are essential for the Website’s smooth operation. Winspark's use of cookies on the website thus falls into the following categories:

  * **Session Management  -** these cookies are essential website usage in general as they manage session information and enable users to navigate through the website.
  * **Functionality  **\- these cookies store information which enables us to remember user preferences e.g. preferred language, sort types, media settings. They are also used to improve users' experience by, for example, stopping users from being shown the same message twice.
  * **Fraud Prevention**  \- these cookies store information which helps us stop fraudulent use of the website.
  * **Tracking  **- these cookies enable us to store information about how users landed on the website for purposes concerning our Affiliates.
  * **Analysis  **– these cookies allow us to recognise and count the number of users, and to see how users move around our website. This helps us to improve the way the website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily; deliver adverts and information more relevant to each user and their interests, and monitor the effectiveness of such adverts and information.

Note that Winspark might, from time to time, use carefully selected third party tracking and/or analytical cookies to assist in improving the website and Winspark’s services for users.  
Where links are provided on the website to third party websites it is important to remember that those websites will have their own cookies and privacy policies which will govern any information you may submit. If you decide to use any linked third party websites, please read their cookies and privacy policies before doing so. 

**How to manage your cookie settings?  **

Please note that we do not recognise or respond to automated browser signals regarding Tracking Technologies, including "Do Not Track" requests. However, there are various ways in which you can manage and control your cookie settings. Please remember that, by deleting or blocking cookies, some of the features of the services may not work properly or as effectively.

**Managing cookies via your web browser   **

Most web browsers will provide you with some general information about cookies; enable you to see what cookies are stored on your device; allow you to retroactively delete cookies (collectively or individually) and enable you to proactively block or allow cookies for all websites or individually selected websites (all through the ‘privacy settings’ paricular to the browser used). Additionally, you can ordinarily turn off third party cookies in a separate setting. 

Information about cookies is usually found in the "Help" section of the web browser. Please note that the settings offered by a browser or device often only apply to that particular browser or device. Below are some links to such settings in some commonly used web browsers:

  * Chrome
  * Chrome for mobile
  * Internet Explorer and Microsoft Edge
  * Mozilla Firefox
  * Safari
  * Opera

_Details of how Winspark protects your privacy are set out in our Privacy Policy above.   _

_Last updated version 3rd September, 2018._
